W.A.C. Bennett fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Premier's subject files, 1939 - 1972; F-55-49; 1.08 m of textual records
  - International Joint Commission Executive Session, 3 October 1951 - 4 October 1951; F-55-49-0-0-47 (Archival box - standard 55-98)
  - Marketing B.C.'s Columbia Downstream Power Benefits, 12 July 1963; F-55-49-0-0-48 (Archival box - standard 55-98)
  - Columbia River Development, 24 March 1964; F-55-49-0-0-49 (Archival box - standard 55-98)
  - Representations made to the Standing Committee on External Affairs, 27 April 1955; F-55-49-0-0-50 (Archival box - standard 55-98)
  - A Survey of the Columbia River Power Potential, 1 August 1960; F-55-49-0-0-51 (Archival box - standard 55-98)
  - Prospectus - British Columbia Hydro and Power Authority, June 1966; F-55-49-0-0-52 (Archival box - standard 55-98)
  - Major Undeveloped Water Powers of Northern BC and What They Mean to the Province, February 1955; F-55-49-0-0-53 (Archival box - standard 55-98)
  - Power from the Peace (brochure), [196-?]; F-55-49-0-0-54 (Archival box - standard 55-98)
  - Eye-Witness Accounts of the Peace River District of B.C., July 1959; F-55-49-0-0-55 (Archival box - standard 55-98)
  - Correspondence, 1963 - 1967; F-55-49-0-0-56 (Archival box - standard 55-98)
  - Review of Power Planning in the Pacific Northwest, 9 March 1965; F-55-49-0-0-57 (Archival box - standard 55-98)
  - Columbia River Development, 23 May 1963; F-55-49-0-0-58 (Archival box - standard 55-98)
  - Notes on the Peace River Project, July 1962; F-55-49-0-0-59 (Archival box - standard 55-98)
  - Preliminary Report on the Development of Moran Damsite, [196-?]; F-55-49-0-0-60 (Archival box - standard 55-98)
  - Brief of Export of Surplus Electric Power, 1960; F-55-49-0-0-61 (Archival box - standard 55-99)
  - Factors Affecting the Cost of Columbia River Power in Canada, May 1961; F-55-49-0-0-62 (Archival box - standard 55-99)
  - Proposal for Construction of Transmission Lines Columbia Project, November 1960; F-55-49-0-0-63 (Archival box - standard 55-99)
  - The Northwest Power Project and its Related Industries, 4 March 1954; F-55-49-0-0-64 (Archival box - standard 55-99)
  - The Columbia River Treaty Protocol and Related Documents, February 1964; F-55-49-0-0-65 (Archival box - standard 55-99)
  - BC Hydro and Power Authority Sinking Fund Bonds - Registered Securities, 2 July 1966; F-55-49-0-0-66 (Archival box - standard 55-99)
  - Peace River Project, Review of Construction Sept. 1961 to March 1969, F-55-49-0-0-67 (Archival box - standard 55-99)
  - Columbia Construction Progress Report No. 1 - Duncan, Arrow, Mica, 1965; F-55-49-0-0-68 (Archival box - standard 55-99)
  - Submission by the Consolidated Mining and Smelting Company of Canada to the BC Energy Board, [196-?]; F-55-49-0-0-69 (Archival box - standard 55-99)
  - Proposal for Engineering Services Columbia River Development, 23 January 1961; F-55-49-0-0-70 (Archival box - small 55-100)
  - The Peace River Project, 17 August 1962; F-55-49-0-0-71 (Archival box - small 55-100)
  - Cooperative Development of the Columbia River Basin, February 1960; F-55-49-0-0-72 (Archival box - small 55-100)
  - The Columbia River Agreement, 10 February 1964; F-55-49-0-0-73 (Archival box - small 55-100)
  - Study of Development of Upper Columbia River Basin, Canada and United States, 1955; F-55-49-0-0-74 (Archival box - small 55-100)
  - Rules of Procedure and Text of Treaty, 1947; F-55-49-0-0-75 (Archival box - small 55-100)
  - Sequence and Timing in River Basin Development, February 1960; F-55-49-0-0-76 (Archival box - small 55-100)
  - U.S. Columbia River Power System 1964 Report, February 1964; F-55-49-0-0-77 (Archival box - small 55-100)
  - U.S. Columbia River Power System 1958 Report, February 1958; F-55-49-0-0-78 (Archival box - small 55-100)
  - B.C. Hydro - Peace River Power, [196-?]; F-55-49-0-0-79 (Archival box - small 55-100)
  - B.C. Hydro - Peace River Power brochure, 1968; F-55-49-0-0-80 (Archival box - small 55-100)
  - Peace River Power - The Portage Mountain Project, 1966; F-55-49-0-0-81 (Archival box - small 55-100)
  - Statement of votes, 1949; F-55-49-0-0-82 (Archival box - standard 55-101)
  - Index of polling divisions South Okanagan, 1952; F-55-49-0-0-83 (Archival box - standard 55-101)
  - Provincial elections, 1953; F-55-49-0-0-84 (Archival box - standard 55-101)
  - Political opinion survey, vol. 1, 1955; F-55-49-0-0-85 (Archival box - standard 55-101)
  - Political opinion survey, vol. 2, 1955; F-55-49-0-0-86 (Archival box - standard 55-101)
  - Political opinion survey, vol. 3, 1955; F-55-49-0-0-87 (Archival box - standard 55-101)
  - Survey voting preferences West Point Grey, 1960; F-55-49-0-0-88 (Archival box - standard 55-101)
  - Province of BC debentures cancelled/destroyed, 1959; F-55-49-0-0-89 (Archival box - standard 55-101)
  - Whatshan Dam inquiry, 1953; F-55-49-0-0-90 (Archival box - small 55-102)
  - Water powers BC Canada, 1954; F-55-49-0-0-91 (Archival box - small 55-102)
  - Hydroelectric potentialities of the upper Fraser, 1956; F-55-49-0-0-92 (Archival box - small 55-102)
  - Flood control and hydro power in Fraser River Basin, 1958; F-55-49-0-0-93 (Archival box - small 55-102)
  - Water license applications filed, 1961; F-55-49-0-0-94 (Archival box - small 55-102)
  - Power of the peace, 1963; F-55-49-0-0-95 (Archival box - small 55-102)
  - Federal provincial conference, 1956; F-55-49-0-0-96 (Archival box - small 55-103)
  - Plenary session, federal provincial conference, 1968; F-55-49-0-0-97 (Archival box - small 55-103)
  - Federal provincial conference, 1971; F-55-49-0-0-98 (Archival box - small 55-103)
- Miscellaneous items - dated, 1952 - 1972; F-55-50; 39 cm of textual records
  Series consists of miscellaneous dated records relating to a range of subjects. Included are correspondence, resolutions, reports, a seating plan, financial statistics, a radio script and radio transcripts, briefs, minutes, itineraries, press releases, plans, statements, proposals, programs, a schedule, notes and an Order-in-Council (copy).
  - Miscellaneous Items - Letters, resolutions. Letters from: W.C. Woodward, Herbert Fiddes, Ralph E. Spencer, Ernest F.W. Hysop, 1952; F-55-50-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 55-78)
  - Miscellaneous Items - Letters, speech, report, seating plan, financial statistics. Letters from: Daisy Daw, Eric Martin, Thomas Uphill, 1953; F-55-50-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 55-78)
  - Miscellaneous Items - Draft of act, reports, speech, resolution, 1954; F-55-50-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 55-78)
  - Miscellaneous Items - Letters, speeches., 1955; F-55-50-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 55-79)
  - Miscellaneous Items - Letters, reports. Letters from: Frank Mackenzie Ross, W.C. Mainwaring, J.B. Feeney, Jean Lesage, T.H. Crosby, H.F. Waste, 1956; F-55-50-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 55-79)
  - Miscellaneous Items - Letters, financial report, radio script, note. Letters from: H.L. Straight, Sigrid Nohr, W. Percy Wright, H.R. Stephen, R.T. Bowman, Edward C. Ertl, J.E. Brown, 1957; F-55-50-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 55-79)
  - Miscellaneous Items - Letters, radio transcripts, report, pamphlet. Letters from: J. Stuart Keate, Alvin Hamilton, W.M. Guild, 1958; F-55-50-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 55-79)
  - Miscellaneous Items - Letters, briefs, minutes, itinerary. Letters from: J.L. Wilson, E.C. Warner, L.L.G. Bentley, G.W.G. McConachie, John Fowler, Donald B. Kennedy, Gerald Bowering, J.V. Fisher, C. Farquharson, R.G. Parkinson, Donald H. Riggan, 1959; F-55-50-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 55-79)
  - Miscellaneous Items - Press release, article, letters. Letters from: Dan Campbell, S. Horace Lewis, R.C. Seed, 1960; F-55-50-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 55-79)
  - Miscellaneous Items - Letters, photographs, draft of speech, plans, statement, pamphlet, file note. Letters from: Joseph F. Buresh, Matthew Dihanits, T.S. McPherson, Ronald B. Worley, 1961; F-55-50-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 55-79)
  - Miscellaneous Items - Letters, proposal, radio transcript, statement. Letters from: Donald Gordon, Ronald B. Worley, Hazel O'Neail, 1962; F-55-50-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 55-79)
  - Miscellaneous Items - Letters, speech, program, television schedule. Letters from: Robert W. Bonner, George Smith, Faye White, Hugh L. Keenleyside, Earle L. Leslie, Ben D. Aird, Frank M. McMahon, 1963; F-55-50-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 55-79)
  - Miscellaneous Items - Letters, program, statement. Letters from: Norman Cribbens, H.W. Mulholland, 1964; F-55-50-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 55-79)
  - Miscellaneous Items - Letters, statements. Letters from: Connie Murphy, Stan Carnell, Antony Vickers, Dion Hamer, Marga Feika, Ronald B. Worley, Irene Wilson, W.W. McPherson, Janet Boylen, Wendy Cook, J.F. McDonald, L.J. Wallace, A. Ikert, 1965; F-55-50-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 55-79)
  - Miscellaneous Items - Letters, newspaper clippings, program. Letters from: A.J. Bowering, Jack Robbins, Twain Sullivan, J.C. Lambie, Leo J. Matte, R.J. Gallagher, D. Corbett, Mrs. John Comeau, Ken M. Kirkby, A. Ikert, Lazelle Charlie, 1966; F-55-50-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 55-80)
  - Miscellaneous Items - Letters, brochure, clipping, program, report, news-letter. Letters from: Gordon M. Shrum, D.E. Smith, Robert Bellinger, George L. Murray, 1967; F-55-50-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 55-80)
  - Miscellaneous Items - Letters, memoranda, financial statistics, statement, speech, press release, reports, motion picture script, message. Letters from: John R. Landis, William C. Mearns, P. Calvet, Isabel P. Dawson, William Clancey, E.E. Ackland, O.D. Cantelon, L.J. Bennett, Sam G. Ross, Donald L. Brothers, Frank Richter, 1968; F-55-50-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 55-80)
  - Miscellaneous Items - Letters, reports, statements, notes, resolutions, air tickets. Letters from: F. Macklin, Allan Bentlay, Angus Carmichael, J.A. Currie, George More, Han Manthei, R.M. Simpson, W.C. Bennett, Doreen F. Druitt, R.A. Dunn, E.L. Reichert, R.A. Gunoff, D. Peters, Agnes M. MacLauchlan, Peter Howes, N. Armstrong, G. Dan Ekman, K.G. Bream, Douglas Henry Tindall, Colleen Brumitt, 1969; F-55-50-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 55-80)
  - Miscellaneous Items - Letters, memoranda, reports, itineraries, newspaper clipping, brochure, policy manual. Letters from: A.W. Nordman, Edmond A. Milroy, A.L. Bocking, E.W. Disher, F. Merlin Hawes, Mrs. Cyril Rash, Anne McDonald, 1970; F-55-50-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 55-80)
  - Miscellaneous Items - Letters, statistics, reports, newspaper clipping, summary, notes. Letters from: D. Roland Michener, Donald A.S. Wilson, J.R. Meredith, W.H. Murray, Cyril M. Shefford, O. Zimmerman, Philip N. Holtby, R.G. Freeman, R.G. Rogers, Dan Campbell, J.C. Hibbard, 1971; F-55-50-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 55-80)
  - Miscellaneous Items - Letters, newsletter, newspaper clippings, pamphlets, music score. Letters from: Terence Ruttle, Grace V. Mitts, Gerald A. Regan, 1972; F-55-50-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 55-80)
  - Miscellaneous Items - Letters, card. Letters from: Emery Barnes, Josephine Crampton, H.G. Bayliss, Lilian Head, Olive R. Neill, Acland Acres, W.S. Cawsey, George Cyril Wuhenyer, R.H. Wagner, Dorothy Wilson, Charles Grabosky, Sybil Chalk, W.S. Greer, Norman Geibert, Valerie A. Wallis, Elsa Drummond, Elizabeth Seaton, Ralph Loffmark, 1972; F-55-50-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 55-80)
  - Miscellaneous Items - Letters, lists, newspaper clippings, 1972; F-55-50-0-0-23 (Archival box - standard 55-80)
  - Election - Letters (including draft of form letter), 1972; F-55-50-0-0-24 (Archival box - standard 55-81)
  - Election - Letters (incoming), 1972; F-55-50-0-0-25 (Archival box - standard 55-81)
  - Election - Letters (incoming), 1972; F-55-50-0-0-26 (Archival box - standard 55-81)
  - Election - Letters (incoming), 1972; F-55-50-0-0-27 (Archival box - standard 55-81)
  - Election - Letters (incoming), cards, 1972; F-55-50-0-0-28 (Archival box - standard 55-81)
  - Election - Letters (incoming), 1972; F-55-50-0-0-29 (Archival box - standard 55-81)
  - Election - Letters (incoming), 1972; F-55-50-0-0-30 (Archival box - standard 55-81)
  - Election - Letters (incoming), 1972; F-55-50-0-0-31 (Archival box - standard 55-81)
  - Election - Letters (incoming), 1972; F-55-50-0-0-32 (Archival box - standard 55-81)
  - Election - Letters (incoming), 1972; F-55-50-0-0-33 (Archival box - standard 55-81)
  - Order-in-Council #3386 - Copies, 1972; F-55-50-0-0-34 (Archival box - standard 55-81)
  - Journal of Commerce, 1971; F-55-50-0-0-35
  - Provincially owned Electric Systems in BC as at 31 Dec 1961, F-55-50-0-0-36
  - Agricultural Maps for City of Kelowna, 1958; F-55-50-0-0-37
- Miscellaneous items - undated, F-55-51; 6 cm of textual records
  Series consists of miscellaneous undated records relating to a range of subjects. Included are statements, lists, financial statistics, letters, statements, notes, itineraries and poems.
  - Miscellaneous - Statements, lists, financial statistics, letters. Letters from: R.T. Bowman, Doris L. Clarke, A. Ikert, Grace McCarthy, Ronald B. Worley, F-55-51-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 55-82)
  - Miscellaneous - Statements, report, F-55-51-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 55-82)
  - Miscellaneous - Speech, statements, F-55-51-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 55-82)
  - Miscellaneous - Letters (no signature or incomplete signature), lists, notes, itineraries, poems, F-55-51-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 55-82)
- Miscellaneous telegrams, 1952 - 1972; F-55-52; 2 cm of textual records
  Series consists of miscellaneous telegrams. Included are congratulatory messages which emanated from federal leaders, royalty, family and many others, and telegrams concerning strikes, potential libel charges and departmental decision-making.
  - Telegrams [no file], 1952 - 1967; F-55-52-0-0-1
  - Telegrams, 1968 - 1972; F-55-52-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 55-82)
- Miscellaneous speeches, 1952 - 1972; F-55-53; 5 cm of textual records
  Series consists of miscellaneous speech texts.
  - Speeches [no file], 1952 - 1959; F-55-53-0-0-1
  - Speeches, 1960 - 1967; F-55-53-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 55-82)
  - Speeches, 1968 - 1972; F-55-53-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 55-82)
  - Speeches, F-55-53-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 55-82)
- Municipal Acts, 1945 - 1957; F-55-54; 26 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records of the Premier's Office relating to the passage of various Municipal Acts. Included are copies of bills, notes on second reading, copies of Acts, draft amendments, and other records.
  - Municipal Acts 1953, 1948 - 1953; F-55-54-1; 3 cm of textual records
    - Assessment Equalization Act, 1953; F-55-54-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 55-83)
    - Irrigation Loan Act Amendment Act, 1953; F-55-54-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 55-83)
    - Logging Tax Act, 1953; F-55-54-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 55-83)
    - Mining Tax Act Amendment Act, 1948 - 1953; F-55-54-1-0-4 (Archival box - standard 55-83)
    - Public Schools Construction Act, 1953; F-55-54-1-0-5 (Archival box - standard 55-83)
    - Social Security and Municipal Aid Tax Act Amendment Act, 1953; F-55-54-1-0-6 (Archival box - standard 55-83)
    - Taxation Act Amendment Act, 1953; F-55-54-1-0-7 (Archival box - standard 55-83)
    - Toll Highways and Bridges Authority Act, 1953; F-55-54-1-0-8 (Archival box - standard 55-83)
  - Municipal Acts 1954, 1948 - 1954; F-55-54-2; 5 cm of textual records
    - Amusement Tax Act Amendment Act, 1954; F-55-54-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 55-83)
    - B.C. Corporation Income Tax Act 1950 Amendment Act, 1954; F-55-54-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 55-83)
    - B.C. Corporation Income Tax Act 1949 Amendment Act, 1954; F-55-54-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 55-83)
    - Highway Development Act Amendment Act, 1954; F-55-54-2-0-4 (Archival box - standard 55-83)
    - Hospital Construction Act Amendment Act, 1954; F-55-54-2-0-5 (Archival box - standard 55-83)
    - Pacific Great Eastern Railway Company Debt Adjustment Act, 1954; F-55-54-2-0-6 (Archival box - standard 55-83)
    - Pacific Great Eastern Railway legislation, 1954; F-55-54-2-0-7 (Archival box - standard 55-83)
    - Pacific Great Eastern Construction Loan Act, 1954; F-55-54-2-0-8 (Archival box - standard 55-83)
    - Public Schools Construction Act Amendment Act, 1954; F-55-54-2-0-9 (Archival box - standard 55-83)
    - Revenue Act Amendment Act, 1954; F-55-54-2-0-10 (Archival box - standard 55-83)
    - Revenue Act Amendment Act, 1948 - 1954; F-55-54-2-0-11 (Archival box - standard 55-83)
    - Social Services Tax Act Amendment Act, 1954; F-55-54-2-0-12 (Archival box - standard 55-83)
  - Municipal Acts 1955, 1948 - 1955; F-55-54-3; 6 cm of textual records
    - Assessment Equalization Act Amendment Act, 1953 - 1955; F-55-54-3-0-1 (Archival box - standard 55-83)
    - B.C. Corporation Income Tax Act Amendment Act, 1948 - 1955; F-55-54-3-0-2 (Archival box - standard 55-83)
    - Electric Power Act Amendment Act, 1948 - 1955; F-55-54-3-0-3 (Archival box - standard 55-83)
    - First Narrows Bridge Company Limited Liquidation Act, 1955; F-55-54-3-0-4 (Archival box - standard 55-83)
    - Gasoline Tax Act Amendment Act, 1948 - 1955; F-55-54-3-0-5 (Archival box - standard 55-83)
    - Logging Tax Act Amendment Act, 1953 - 1955; F-55-54-3-0-6 (Archival box - standard 55-83)
    - Municipalities Aid Act, 1948 - 1955; F-55-54-3-0-7 (Archival box - standard 55-83)
    - Pacific Great Eastern Construction Loan Act Amendment Act, 1954 - 1955; F-55-54-3-0-8 (Archival box - standard 55-83)
    - Revenue Surplus Appropriation Act Amendment Act, 1952 - 1955; F-55-54-3-0-9 (Archival box - standard 55-83)
    - Social Services Tax Act Amendment Act, 1954 - 1955; F-55-54-3-0-10 (Archival box - standard 55-83)
    - Taxation Act Amendment Act, 1953 - 1955; F-55-54-3-0-11 (Archival box - standard 55-84)
    - Toll Highways and Bridges Authority Act Amendment Act, 1953 - 1955; F-55-54-3-0-12 (Archival box - standard 55-84)
    - Unclaimed Money Deposits Act Amendment Act, 1955; F-55-54-3-0-13 (Archival box - standard 55-84)
    - Village Municipalities Assistance Act Amendment Act, 1953 - 1955; F-55-54-3-0-14 (Archival box - standard 55-84)
  - Municipal Acts 1956, 1945 - 1956; F-55-54-4; 4 cm of textual records
    - Amusements Tax Act Amendment Act, 1948 - 1956; F-55-54-4-0-1 (Archival box - standard 55-84)
    - Assessment Equalization Act Amendment Act, 1956; F-55-54-4-0-2 (Archival box - standard 55-84)
    - Centennial Celebration Act, 1956; F-55-54-4-0-3 (Archival box - standard 55-84)
    - Gasoline Tax Act Amendment Act, 1955 - 1956; F-55-54-4-0-4 (Archival box - standard 55-84)
    - Housing Act Amendment Act, 1950 - 1956; F-55-54-4-0-5 (Archival box - standard 55-84)
    - Improvement Districts Assistance Loan Act Amendment Act, 1945 - 1956; F-55-54-4-0-6 (Archival box - standard 55-84)
    - Municipalities Aid Act Amendment Act, 1955 - 1956; F-55-54-4-0-7 (Archival box - standard 55-84)
    - Power Act Amendment Act, 1955 - 1956; F-55-54-4-0-8 (Archival box - standard 55-84)
    - Supply Act, 1956; F-55-54-4-0-9 (Archival box - standard 55-84)
    - Taxation Act Amendment Act, 1956; F-55-54-4-0-10 (Archival box - standard 55-84)
    - Toll Highways and Bridges Authority Act Amendment Act, 1953 - 1956; F-55-54-4-0-11 (Archival box - standard 55-84)
  - Municipal Acts 1957, 1948 - 1957; F-55-54-5; 8 cm of textual records
    - Agent-General Act Amendment Act, 1948 - 1956; F-55-54-5-0-1 (Archival box - standard 55-84)
    - Assessment Equalization Act Amendment Act, 1954 - 1957; F-55-54-5-0-2 (Archival box - standard 55-84)
    - Cemeteries Act Amendment Act, 1948 - 1957; F-55-54-5-0-3 (Archival box - standard 55-84)
    - Centennial Celebration Act Amendment Act, 1957; F-55-54-5-0-4 (Archival box - standard 55-84)
    - Department of Recreation and Conservation Act, 1957; F-55-54-5-0-5 (Archival box - standard 55-84)
    - Federal-Provincial Agreement Act, 1957; F-55-54-5-0-6 (Archival box - standard 55-84)
    - Fort Langley Agreement Act, 1957; F-55-54-5-0-7 (Archival box - standard 55-84)
    - Insurance Premiums Tax Act, 1957; F-55-54-5-0-8 (Archival box - standard 55-84)
    - Logging Tax Act Amendment Act, 1953 - 1957; F-55-54-5-0-9 (Archival box - standard 55-84)
    - Mineral Property Taxation Act, 1957; F-55-54-5-0-10 (Archival box - standard 55-84)
    - Mining Tax Act Amendment Act, 1957; F-55-54-5-0-11 (Archival box - standard 55-84)
    - Motor Carrier Act Amendment Act, 1956 - 1957; F-55-54-5-0-12 (Archival box - standard 55-84)
    - Municipal Cemeteries Act Amendment Act, 1948 - 1957; F-55-54-5-0-13 (Archival box - standard 55-84)
    - Pacific Great Eastern Construction Loan Act Amendment Act, 1954 - 1957; F-55-54-5-0-14 (Archival box - standard 55-84)
    - Power Act Amendment Act, 1955 - 1957; F-55-54-5-0-15 (Archival box - standard 55-84)
    - Provincial Home-owner Grant Act, 1957; F-55-54-5-0-16 (Archival box - standard 55-84)
    - Public Utilities Act Amendment Act, 1956 - 1957; F-55-54-5-0-17 (Archival box - standard 55-84)
    - Supply Act, 1957; F-55-54-5-0-18 (Archival box - standard 55-84)
    - Taxation Act Amendment Act, 1957; F-55-54-5-0-19 (Archival box - standard 55-84)
    - Village Municipalities Assistance Act Amendment Act, 1948 - 1957; F-55-54-5-0-20 (Archival box - standard 55-84)
- Audio recordings, 1930 - 1979; F-55-56; 23 sound recordings; Physical description: sound recordings consist of 30 audio reels and 1 audio cassette. With the exception of one reel, the contents of all the reels are fully discernible. The sound quality is fair on most of the reels. However, a substantial minority are of a poor quality. Such reels are typically second-hand recordings, reels recorded at a very low volume, or recordings which have tones or other sounds playing in the background.
  Series consists of audio recordings presented to or regarding W.A.C. Bennett. Items were produced primarily by radio stations, although some were created by private citizens.
  The series focuses on a variety of subject matters regarding Bennett. The majority of the reels document tributes and dinners which were given in honour of the Premier. Several of the reels also document interviews with Bennett as well as many radio commentaries on his performance as Premier. Finally, a significant number of reels document political functions and gatherings which Bennett attended. These include the Ottawa Conference on the Constitution, a Social Credit leadership convention, and the provincial Social Credit convention of 1963.
  Recordings have been placed in four organizational categories, according to reel size. Items in category I are 3" in size; reels in category II are 4" in size; reels in category III are 5" in size; and reels in category IV are 7" in size. The series also includes one audiocassette, which has been placed in the first category.
  - Premier W.A.C. Bennett – testimonial dinner (CKWX recording), February 17, 1965; F-55-56-0-0-0-10 (Audio reel OBJ-977, Audio reel OBJ-967, Audio reel OBJ-968)
    CKWX Radio; Bennett, W.A.C.; Sound recordings
    Duration: 2
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-55-item107, F-55-item135, F-55-item136, IV-1, IV-2, IV-6, IV-7, IV-11, IV-13.
  - A Tribute to Arthur Laing, September 22, 1974; F-55-56-0-0-0-22 (Audio reel OBJ-971)
    CJJC Radio; Jacques, Roy; Lord, Brian; Laing, Arthur; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-55-item94, IV-8.
  - Vancouver Board of Trade testimonial dinner for Premier Bennett, November 4, 1971; F-55-56-0-0-0-19 (Audio reel OBJ-972)
    Vancouver Board of Trade; CKNW Radio; Bennett, W.A.C.; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-55-item96, IV-12.